But you never thought of the a redundant umbrella.
但你从来没有想到过一个多余的雨伞
Most AWS services are either inherently redundant or can be configured to be redundant.
大多数 AWS 服务本身都是冗余的 或者可以配置为冗余
It will be important that you learn to recognize which
重要的是你必须学会承认
services come redundant by default and which do not.
服务在缺省情况下会出现冗余 而不会出现冗余
Most services have a varying degree of redundancy.
大多数服务具有不同程度的冗余
You can make cost versus benefit decisions for your use case.
您可以为您的用例做出成本与效益决策
Sometimes, high availability is absolutely critical.
有时 高可用性绝对至关重要
Sometimes, it's just nice to have,
有时候真的很高兴
and sometimes it's unnecessary.
有时是不必要的
Costs often plays a factor in these decisions.
成本往往在这些决策中发挥作用
To have a service run in a ultra redundant, active,
要使服务在超冗余的活动中运行
active multi-region configuration always cost more
活动多区域配置总是花费更多
than running it on a single application server in one availability zone.
而不是在一个可用性区域中的单个应用程序服务器上运行
There are circumstances for both.
这两种情况都有
You must decide and be able to justify that decision.
你必须做出决定 并能够为这一决定辩护
Also, consider what is required for a given use case.
另外 请考虑给定用例的必需内容